翻译: 元气 longli Melanie
各位 注意了
Attention, everyone!
和你们熟知且深爱的Jake Peralta告别吧
Say good-bye to the Jake Peralta you know and love,
因为今天起我就再也不是原来的我了
for today is the day I forever change.
校对: 番茄滚滚
喔 你终于要留胡子了吗
Ooh, are you finally growing a mustache?
不 你知道我留不起来
No, you know I can't do that,
后期: 尘世劫
还老戳我痛处 太残忍了
and it's cruel of you to keep bringing it up.
这份信封里是我叔叔留给我的遗产
This envelope contains the inheritance my uncle left me.
他一年前过世 身前相当有钱
He died a year ago; he was so rich,
压制: 发烧
他甚至有一个专门用来吃饭的房间
he had a whole room in his house just to eat in.
就是餐厅呗
You mean like a dining room?
- 没错 但是在曼哈顿  - 哇哦 牛
- Yeah, but in Manhattan. - Oh, dang.
但是 我不会因为有钱了
Now, just because I'm definitely rich now
就忘记我的根
doesn't mean I'm gonna forget my roots.
你们都能分一杯羹 尽情说吧
You all get something, so fire away.
Jake 我俩的友谊就是你给我的最好的礼物了
Jake, your friendship is gift enough for me.
友谊算屁 我要杜卡迪摩托车 怪兽821型号的
Friendship is crap. I want a Ducati Monster 821.
没问题 给Rosa一辆摩托车
All right, Rosa gets a motorcycle.
酷 我想要辆跑车
Oh, cool. I want a fast sports car.
得了吧 说实话
Come on. You can be honest.
我想要古老昂贵的书籍 我给你列个清单
I want old, expensive books. I'll send you a list.
这还差不多
There you go.
现在 来看看我身价多少
Now, let's find out what I'm worth.
我紧张得打不开了 警长 你来
Oh, I'm too nervous to open it. Sarge, you do it.
好
Okay.
是股票 一百万股
It's stock. One million shares!
天哪
Oh, my God!
Blockbuster Video 英国DVD租赁公司 2013年破产
大片租赁的股票
Of Blockbuster Video stock.
- 哦  - 怎么了 这股不好吗
- Ohh. - What? Is that bad?
我还有张大片租赁的卡
I still have a Blockbuster card!
大片租赁怎么了
What happened to Blockbuster?
神烦警探
第三季 第十八集
电波诚译
第99片区
上午8:21
绘图绘图绘图绘图绘图绘图
Mapping, mapping, mapping, mapping, mapping, mapping.
干嘛呢 老兄
What's going on there, buddy?
在激光手术失败眼球烧毁前
Just making a final imprint of your face
把你的面庞
before the LASIK surgery goes poorly
深深印在我的脑海里
and my eyeballs get burned off.
别局限于眼球 最好全脸烧毁
Why stop at the eyes? Burn off your whole head.
Charles 手术会成功的
Charles, the surgery is going to go fine, all right?
你的视力会受损几个小时而已
You'll have some vision impairment for a few hours,
那段时间我会一直陪着你的
and I'm gonna be with you the whole time!
再说 医生还会给你配<机械战警>里
Plus, they're gonna give you some of those sweet-ass
狂拽炫酷的墨镜
Robocop sunglasses.
那是给盲人的墨镜
Those are blind people sunglasses.
警监 你在这儿干什么
Captain. What are you doing here?
我以为你请假收拾行李 准备远行去了
Thought you took the day off to pack for your big trip,
还是你终于明白
or did you finally realize
打包只要一分钟就能搞定了
that it only takes one minute to pack?
要是你在乎自己的物品以及
Not if you care about your possessions
别人看你的眼光 一分钟绝对不够
and what the world sees when they look at you.
- 哼  - 我不去了
- Huh. - I'm not going.
Cheddar固定的狗保姆病了
Cheddar's regular dog sitter is ill,
我家的暖气也没了
and the heat's out in my house,
我觉得现在不是去巴黎看Kevin的好时机
so I don't think it's a good time for me to visit Kevin in Paris.
你不能说取消就取消啊
Sir, you can't just cancel your trip.
你俩已经好几个月没见了
You guys haven't seen each other in months.
这么着吧
How about this?
我和Amy会在你走后帮你看家的
Amy and I will look after your house while you're gone.
- 没错吧 Ames  - 完全没问题
- Right, Ames? - Totally.
我以为你俩要照看Ray Charles Boyle
I thought you two were watching Ray Charles Boyle.
有理
Good point.
Charles可以跟我们一起照看Cheddar
Charles can come with us and look after Cheddar.
我听说盲人
I'm told that blind people
和狗之间都有特殊的联系
have a special connection with dogs.
我就知道 你真觉得我会瞎
I knew it. You do think I'm gonna go blind.
你的提议很好
That's an interesting offer,
但我不想强人所难
but I don't want to be an imposition.
呸 强人所难 没有的事
Pshaw! Imposition? Pshaw!
不 我在说Santiago
No, I was talking to Santiago.
我有预感事情她会全包
I assume she'll be doing all the work.
为什么
Why?
因为我们过去的记录和性格咯
Oh, because of our track records and personalities.
是是是 有理有据
Sure, sure, sure, sure, yeah.
那么 Santiago 你真的没问题吗
So, Santiago, are you sure you're okay with this?
绝对没问题 简直是美差
I'm so in. This is gonna be fantastic.
糟透了 我们都没准备好
This is horrible! We're not ready for this.
这是个一级职责
This is a level one responsibility.
我顶多是个二级人手 而你连级都没有
I'm a level two at best, and you're not even a level!
我有级
Well, I'm a level, you know.
大概 五级的样子
I'm probably, like, a level five.
不 算
Not a level.
我就知道你会紧张过度
I thought you'd be psyched.
在Holt警监家待一个礼拜啊
I mean, a week at Captain Holt's house?
你不就想在他家度蜜月吗
Wasn't that where you wanted to spend your honeymoon?
是没错 但是这简直压力山大啊
Yeah, but this is too much pressure!
你为什么要自告奋勇啊
Why did you volunteer us for this?
因为Holt已经好几个月没见着Kevin了
Because Holt hasn't seen Kevin in, like, months,
我当时就想 如果是我俩
and I was just thinking if that was me and you,
我一定会很伤心
it would make me really sad.
喔 你好贴心哦
Oh. That's actually super sweet.
而且 还有本又厚又重的活页夹
Plus, there's this big, fat binder
里面全是指示和规则
full of instructions and rules.
还有本活页夹
There's a binder?
你怎么不早说 笨蛋
Why didn't you lead with that, you idiot?
我还是让你俩单独呆着吧
I'm just gonna leave you two alone.
好哒
Okay.
Diaz
Diaz.
Pimento
Pimento.
- 好  - 你好
- What's up? - What's up with you?
- 给我的报告签个字  - 好
- I need you to sign this report. - Okay.
我给你签
I'll sign your report.
什么鬼
What the hell?
当心 墨水还没干
Careful. The ink's still wet.
也许这样干得快
Maybe this'll help.
够了 他们不能再这样了
Okay, they got to knock that off.
- 放轻松 警长  - 夏日之恋 小亲亲
- Loosen up, Sarge. - Summer of love, baby.
现在是三月 闭嘴吧你们
It's March, man. Shut up.
他们说得没错
It's true what they say.
因为我彻底瞎了
Now that I'm fully blind forever,
我的其他感官变敏锐了
my other senses are heightened.
我摸到了一扇门
I feel a door.
我们到Holt警监家了
We're at Captain Holt's house.
刚才停车的时候GPS就说了
Also, the GPS announced it when we pulled up.
我们进去以后
Hey, once we're inside,
就管好自己的手别乱摸了 好吗
maybe keep your hands to yourself, all right?
警监对自己的东西讲究得很
The captain can be very particular about his stuff.
Cheddar 松开 快松开
Cheddar! Let go! Let go of it!
- Amy  - 这可是件羊绒衫
- Amy? - This is a cashmere sweater!
我特么又过敏了
Oh, my stupid allergies!
他跑进了Kevin的衣柜
He got into Kevin's closet.
他本该待在楼下的
He was supposed to stay downstairs.
活页夹里写得清清楚楚
The binder was very clear about that.
你为什么不能尊重一下活页夹
Why won't you respect the binder?
糟了 他把所有的高领毛衣都咬成普通领子了
Oh, no, he's turning all the turtlenecks into regular necks.
- Charles 你得帮帮我们  - 来了
- Charles, you got to help us. - On it.
和狗相处的关键就是明确谁才是头儿
Okay, the key with dogs is establishing the alpha.
Cheddah 松口 请松口
Cheddah, dwop it. Pwease dwop it.
你想要什么我都给你
I'll give you anything you want.
Cheddar才是头儿 真没想到
Oh, Cheddar is the alpha. Didn't expect that.
求你求你求你
Pwease, pwease, pwease.
好样的 Boyle 有用了
Nice job, Boyle. It worked.
但是一团乱 Jake 家里一团糟啊
But the mess, Jake. The mess!
别急 我们会收拾的
Don't worry. We're gonna clean it up.
一切尽在掌握
Everything is totally under control.
- Charles的裤子着火了  - 什么
- Charles' pants are on fire. - What?
Boyle 电暖气 快离开电暖气
Boyle, the space heater! Get away from the space heater!
我不知道电暖气在哪儿
I don't know where it is!
我只能尽全力跑了
I'm just gonna run at full speed!
- 别  - 疼
- No! - Aah!
Charles 待在原地别动
Charles, just stay where you are!
我来搞定
I got it.
呼 好了
Whoo! Okay.
没事了 一切都没事了
It's okay. Everything's fine.
火也灭了 桌子也
Fire's out. And this table is...
卧槽
Oh!
不怎么结实 我本来要说不怎么结实
Fragile. I was gonna say fragile.
真说中了
Nailed it.
你在打孔
You punching holes?
- 是的  - 纸太多了
- Yeah. - That's way too much paper.
对我来说不算多
Not for me.
喝杯咖啡都不让人消停
Can't even get a cup of coffee.
我要去拿点纸来
Well, I'm off to find some yellow paper
这样就能再做一次了
so I can do this all over again.
好了 Diaz 你够了
All right, Diaz? That's it.
你俩怎么回事
What's going on with you two?
- 你也发现了  - 废话
- Oh, you noticed it? - Yeah, I noticed it!
谁看不见
Everyone's noticed it!
有个变态罪犯问我你俩能不能消停一下
A convicted pervert asked me if you guys could cool it.
我无话可说
I don't know what to tell you.
我俩之间 警长
Something between us, Sarge.
深不可测又岌岌可危
Something dark and urgent.
好啦 好消息
Okay. Great news.
运动裤和腿毛烧焦的味道
The smell of burnt sweatpants and singed leg hair
终于散了
is finally dissipating.
但愿在穿泳衣的季节前能长出来
I just hope I can grow it back by Speedo season.
Raymond Holt来电 手机
Call from Raymond Holt, mobile.
不不 别是Holt啊
Oh, no. Not Holt.
别担心 我来接
Don't worry. I've got this.
您好 警监 今晚您想跟我一起睡觉吗（法语）
Bonjour, Captain. Voulez-vous coucher avec moi?
不 我不想和你睡
No, I don't want to sleep with you.
这句话是这个意思啊
Is that what that means?
老天 我以前那个网球教练真恶心
Oh, man, I had a really gross tennis instructor.
上飞机前我打个电话查看一下
I'm calling to check in before I get on the flight.
- 一切都好吗  - 好
- Everything okay? - Okay?
这么说吧 要是你家房子能说话 她会说
Let's just say if the house could talk, she would say,
"我从没这么高兴过 我爱死Jake了"
"I've never been happier; I love Jake."
有意思
Oh, that's interesting,
我倒是觉得房子会说"Jake大骗子 我失火了"
because I think the house might say "Jake's a liar, and I'm... on fire."
你说啥
What's that now?
保安公司打电话给我说了报警器响了的事
The security company called me about the alarm.
好吧 其实房子没着火
Okay, the house was never on fire.
着火的是Charles的裤子
Charles was on fire, and only on his pants,
然后被我们扑灭了
and we put it out.
我现在要回家了
I'm coming home right now.
等下长官 别这样
Wait, no. Sir, please don't do that.
你得去见Kevin 什么事都没出
You have to go see Kevin. Everything's fine.
不 我已经决定了 我要推迟航班了
No, my decision is final. I'm postponing my flight.
再见 Jacob
Good-bye, Jacob.
不长官 啊
No, sir! Please, please... ahh!
他管我叫"Jacob"
He said "Jacob."
要出大事了
It's biblical.
伙计们
Guys, guys!
Holt正在回家路上
Holt is headed home right now.
不 他不能回家
No! He can't come home.
我们没关大门 狗跑出去了
We left the door open, and the dog ran out.
什么 Cheddar丢了吗
What? We lost Cheddar?
你们突然沉默了我很难解读
These silences are very hard for me to read.
- 你们怎么了  - 我们崩溃了 Charles
- What's the vibe in here? - We're freaking out, Charles!
下午好 感谢你们的加入
Good afternoon. Thank you all for joining me.
我们现在面临的是犯人出逃的情况
What we have here is a fugitive situation.
目标已经出逃30分钟了
Our man has been on the run for 30 minutes.
还有 我们的目标是一只狗
Also, our man is a dog.
我知道你们某些人会想
Now, I know what some of you are thinking:
"谁在乎 只是个宠物"
"Who cares? It's just a pet."
没人这么想 你个禽兽
No one was thinking that, you monster.
不错 刚才是个测试
Good. That was a test.
柯基的平均移动速度是每小时十英里
Now, the average foot speed of a corgi is ten miles per hour,
这意味着每耽搁一秒
which means with every passing second,
那个狡猾的畜生就跑的越远
that slippery bastard gets farther away.
Holt警监还不知道Cheddar失踪了
Captain Holt does not know Cheddar is missing...
但是他会发现的
but he's gonna find out.
天啊 我感觉魔鬼在我胸上跳舞
Oh, God, I feel like the devil is dancing on my chest.
没关系Amy 我们还有时间
It's all right, Amy. We have time.
Gina在去机场接Holt警监的路上
Gina's picking Holt up at the airport,
她说可以拖住警监至少两小时
and she told me she can stall him for at least two hours.
可以 但是我得毁了你的车
I'll do it, but I'm gonna have to total your car.
或者你开慢点就行了
Or you could just drive slowly.
哈哈 她要把你的车变成残骸
Ha-ha, she's gonna wreck your car.
现在我们这样
Here's where we're at.
Amy和我带着瞎子Charles
Amy and I will take Blind Charles
在附近搜索
and search the neighborhood.
Diaz Pimento
Diaz, Pimento...
把狗带回来
Bring the dog back,
活要见狗 死要见尸
dead or alive.
什么 我本来要说张贴寻狗启示
What? No. I was gonna say hang posters.
Terry 还是和他们一起去吧 确保没有伤亡
Terry, maybe go with them, make sure nobody gets killed.
或者我可以加入精神面貌完全不同的另一组
Or maybe I could join another group with a different kind of energy?
Jake 我和Hitchcock怎么办
Jake, what about me and Hitchcock?
你们俩拿一些Chedder的零食
You two grab Cheddar's treats
放在外面的一个碗里
and put 'em in a bowl outside.
你是说那些不够咸的小香肠吗
You mean the little sausage ones that need way more salt?
又想了一下 或许你们还是坐在原地
On second thought, maybe just sit exactly where you are
不要碰任何东西
and don't touch anything.
真好
Sweet.
好了伙计们 是时候了
All right, everyone, it's time to do this.
为了Holt警监 Kevin 和美利坚
For Captain Holt, for Kevin, for America!
上吧 九九片区
Let's go, Nine-Nine!
这队伍长的没边了
This line is interminable.
按照这个速率 我们54分钟以后才能到家
At this rate, we'll be home in 54 minutes
而不是通常的46分钟
instead of the usual 46.
如果我什么都不做的话 是的
Not if I have anything to do with it.
看我的
Watch me now!
不Gina 走错了
No, Gina, the wrong way.
不Gina 小心道钉
No, Gina, the spikes!
偶哦
Uh-oh.
根本不成问题
Well, not a problem.
我只用两个轮子就能带你回家
I can get you home on two wheels.
现在后排轮胎也扎坏了
And that was the second pair of tires.
我自己也能做
I could've done that.
是 我知道你可以
Yeah, I know you could've.
但是你没有做 我做了
But you didn't. I did.
我说 还有很多别的杆子呢
I mean, there are lots of other poles, guys.
整条街都是
A whole street full of 'em.
所以 Adrian
So, Adrian,
我们什么时候停止胡闹做"正"事
when are we gonna stop messing around and do this thing?
呃
Um...
- 绝不  - 什么
- N-never. - What?
我刚想起来
You know what? I just realized.
我有东西忘在家里了  我得
I forgot something at home. I'm just gonna...
真奇怪 你还好么
That was weird. You okay?
是的
Yes.
我们刚接到线报
All right, according to the call we just got on the tip line,
有人说他们看见Cheddar出现在这个街区
someone said they saw Cheddar on this block.
我往北 Jake你往西
I'll head north. Jake, you head west.
半小时后见
We'll meet back in a half hour.
不错 我应该往哪个方向
Great, which direction should I go?
怎么了 我可以听见你们嘴唇在动
What's going on? I can hear your lips moving.
呃 你们在接吻么
Ah! Are you guys kissing?
什么 没有
What? No.
Charles 别总是问这个
Charles, stop always asking that.
抱歉 但是你必须待在车里
Look, I'm sorry, but you have to stay in the car.
这是个错误
That's a mistake!
我的超级感官是一把利器
My super senses are a tool you can't afford to leave
你不能把它留在工具箱里
in the tool chest.
把我从箱子里拿出来 别在你的腰上
Take me out of the box and put me on your belt.
抱歉 但是你只会拖累我们
I'm sorry, but you'd only slow us down.
这么一来Cheddar就称心如意了
And that's exactly what Cheddar wants.
没错
That's right.
我盯上你了 你这个狡猾的畜生
I'm onto you, you slippery little bastard.
Gina 快点
Gina, come on.
你可以在车上玩你的网络社交
You can do your Internet socializing in the truck.
好 我先系一下鞋带
Okay, cool, I just have to tie my shoe real quick.
正在系
Tying it.
打给Jake  Peralta
Call Jake Peralta.
Gine 嘿 拖延战术怎么样了
Gina, hey, how's the stalling?
还不错 拖车刚刚来了
Great; the tow truck just got here,
这能给我们争取至少一个小时
so that'll buy us at least an hour.
拖车 你把我的车怎么样了
Tow truck? What the hell did you do to my car?
贱人 我告诉你了我要毁了你的车
Bitch, I told you I was gonna wreck it.
你说了 你说了
You did. You did.
好吧 我们正要去跟进一条线索
All right, well, we're about to go follow up on a lead right now.
很好 我要从你的仪表板里扯一堆线出来
Great; I'm gonna rip a bunch of wires out of your dashboard.
什么 不 Gina
What? No, don't! Gina...
我什么也没找到 你找到Cheddar了吗
I got nothing. Did you find Cheddar?
差不多 我找到了Shredder
Close. I found Shredder.
Shredder 不 Shredder
Shredder, no! No, Shredder!
你不是Cheddar
You're not Cheddar!
我知道情况看起来很差 但我们要找到他
I know it looks bad, but we're gonna find him.
在我们找到Charles之后
Right after we find Charles.
Charles没了 我们弄丢了Charles
Charles is gone. We lost Charles.
- 什么  - Charles Charles
- What? - Charles? Charles!
这儿 宝贝
Here, boy!
到这儿来 宝贝
我应该意识到我会弄丢Charles
Oh, I should've known I was gonna lose Charles.
他太小了简直可以藏在任何地方
He's so pocket-sized. He could be hidden anywhere!
Jake 我们得把重心放在Cheddar身上
Jake, we need to focus on Cheddar.
Charles是个成人了 他能自己照顾自己
Charles is a grown man. He can take care of himself.
不他不是 他只是一只Charles好么
No, he's not. He's a Charles, all right?
他还瞎了
And he's blind!
天啊  他可能已经死了
Oh, God, he's probably already dead.
是吗 那我们别浪费资源找他了
Right? So let's not waste any resources on him.
等一下 是Charles
Wait, it's Charles.
- Charles  - Jake 是你吗
- Charles? - Jake? Is that you?
我看不见我的电话
I can't see my phone.
我已经播了超过40个错误号码了
I've dialed over 40 wrong numbers.
- 是我  - 我找到Cheddar了
- It's me. - I found Cheddar.
他找到Cheddar了
He found Cheddar!
这就是为什么我说 "我们得去找他"
Which is why I was like, "We need to go to him."
Charles 你在哪
Charles, where are you?
我把他堵在一堆灌木丛里
I've got him cornered in some bushes,
但是我不知道我在哪
but I don't know where I am, and my...
等下 别说话
Wait, stop talking.
我听见了什么背景里的声音
I'm hearing something in the background.
那是什么 一辆火车和一个呜咽的女孩
What is that, a train and a girl whimpering?
是我 我太害怕你找不到我了
That's me; I'm so scared you're not gonna find me.
Charles别动 我知道你的确切位置了
Charles, don't move. I know exactly where you are.
他在第七街入口处
He's at the entrance by 7th Street.
我曾经老去那玩
I used to hang out there all the time.
玩什么
Doing what?
嗷 我玩脱了
Aw! I boofed it.
没什么 很酷的 做爱做的事
Nothing. Cool stuff. Having sex.
总之不重要 我们快走
Anyways, it doesn't matter. Let's go.
- 啊  - 嘿警长
- Aah! - Hey, Sarge.
- 我一直在等你  - 在这
- I've been waiting for you. - In here?
嗯我想单独和你谈谈
Yeah, I wanted to have a private conversation.
你认为Diaz有没有注意
Do you think Diaz noticed
当她约我出去的时候我吓了一跳
that I freaked out a little when she asked me out?
你是说你的眼球从眼眶里冒出来
You mean the way your eyes popped out of your head
然后你转身就跑吗
and you sprinted away at full speed?
- 是 我觉得她注意到了  - 该死
- Yeah, I think she noticed. - Damn it.
我现在很混乱
I'm in kind of a weird head space right now.
有很多情感上的事要处理
I've got a lot on my plate, emotionally speaking.
调情是一回事 但是谈恋爱完全是另一码事
And flirting's one thing, but a relationship?
好吧
Well...
我上一次爱上的人是Katya
The last time I let myself fall for someone was Katya.
她是垃圾箱俱乐部的侍应
She was a bartender at the Garbage Box,
那是一个二流的脱衣舞夜店 我和我从前的那帮"兄弟"经常去
second-rate strip club my mob buddies and I used to go to.
她是个可爱的女孩 但我没能救她离开钢管
She was a sweet girl, but I couldn't save her from the pole.
- 噢她开始跳脱衣舞了吗  - 没
- Oh, she started stripping? - Nope.
老板发现她谎报小费之后 把她钉在了钢管上了
Boss impaled her on a pole when he caught her skimming tips.
天啊
Ooh! Damn, dude.
卧底12年之后再回来对谁都不是件容易的事
Look, coming back from 12 years undercover is not easy for anyone.
我确定Diaz会理解的
I'm sure Diaz gets it.
她太注重情感了
She's so in touch with her feelings.
而且我 哼
And me, hmm.
在经历过做过这么多事后
After what I've seen, after what I've done,
我不知道我还配不配开心起来
I don't know that I deserve to be happy.
你当然可以
Of course you do.
哈
Huh.
我从没有这么想过
I never looked at it that way.
哇 这简直改变了一切
Wow. That changes everything.
哈
Ha!
我根本没说完我的想法
I never even finished my point.
不 警长 你已经说了一切
No, Sarge, you said it all.
你改变了我的人生
You just changed my life.
他一定在这附近
He's got to be here somewhere.
嘿 Peralta
What's up, Peralta?
要过来和我们一起玩吗
Want to jump in on this tasty sesh?
额 你认错人了 我从来没见过你们
Uh, you got the wrong guy. I've never seen you before.
一群傻货
Heh, dumb stoner.
- 他叫了你的名字啊  - 嘿 Charles在这儿呢
- He referred to you by name. - Hey, there's Charles.
- Jake Jake  - Charles 我们在你身后
- Jake? Jake? - Charles, we're behind you.
看 我找到Cheddar啦
Look! I found Cheddar.
- 我找着他了  - 天呐
- I found him. - Oh, God.
我知道 超厉害 有没有
I know. Pretty impressive, right?
今天 是所有盲人都值得骄傲的日子
It's a proud day for blind people everywhere.
- Charles  - 这可不轻松啊
- Charles... - It wasn't easy, though.
这家伙还奋力抗争来着
This guy put up quite a fight.
但我们现在是好朋友了 对吗
But we're good friends now, right?
是谁一直在亲我啊
Right? You gave me a bunch of kisses.
是你一直在亲我啊
You gave me a bunch of kisses.
该死的 Charles 你手上是只负鼠
Damn it, Charles, it's a possum.
哦不要啊
Oh, no.
幸运的是所有轮胎都换成新的了
Mercifully, the tires have been replaced,
所以可以把钥匙给我了吗
so may I please have the keys?
好 但是在我们出发之前
Okay, but before we go,
可以让我在礼品店里选一款不错的空气清新剂吗
can we just choose a nice air freshener from the gift shop?
你永远不会知道什么时候你会找到你的专属香气
You never know when you're gonna find your signature scent.
我不是傻子 Gina 我知道
I'm not an idiot, Gina; I know for a fact
你已经找到了你的专属香气了
you've already found your signature scent.
啊 我真的得开始活的低调一点
Ugh! I have got to stop living my life out loud.
今天真是糟糕透顶
I've had a hell of a day.
我的生活中有好多乱子
I've got a lot going on in my life,
比Peralta毁了我家还要糟糕
more than Peralta ruining my house,
所以拜托你不要再演了
so can we please drop the charade
让我快点回家
so I can get home already?
没问题 先生
Absolutely, sir.
等等 也许我应该告诉你
Wait, I should tell you.
以防你对我动真格
Before you got real with me...
其实我把这些电线都拔出来了
I did rip out all these wires.
所有人 认真听我说
All right, everyone, listen up.
现在的情况是这样的
Here's where we're at.
有个坏消息 Cheddar依然在逃
Bad news. Cheddar is still at large,
那个狡猾的畜生
and you know that slippery little bastard
正在嘲笑我们呢
is just laughing at us.
我们需要一个新的计划 现在就要
We need a new plan, and we need it now.
因为局势越来越紧迫 我无法呼吸了
Because the walls are closing in and I can't breathe.
开始吧 大家想到什么就说什么
Come on, guys, we're just spitballing.
没有什么对或错
There's no stupid ideas.
我们可以穿着Holt警监的衣服在这附近转转
What if we walk around the neighborhood in Captain Holt's clothes,
等着Cheddar闻着气味而来
wait till Cheddar picks up the smell?
不行 这简直是傻了 我们不会这样做的
No, that's insane, never gonna happen.
- 还有谁有想法  - 你们可以销声匿迹
- Anyone else? - You guys go off the grid.
我在听 继续说
I'm listening. Go on.
我可以帮你们搞到墨西哥护照
I get you guys Mexican passports.
完全无法追踪的那种
Totally untraceable.
我们会在公寓纵火制造你们的假死
We fake your death in an apartment fire.
我需要你们每个人给我三颗牙齿
I'll need three teeth from both of you.
然后你们就消失了
Then you guys just disappear.
很简单 我以前试过
It's easy. I've done it before.
哦 真的吗
Oh, have you?
你真的"没有"提到这件事整整500次
Because you haven't mentioned it 500 times.
- 说点新鲜的  - 好吧
- Get a new thing. - Okay.
简直不敢相信 穿着Holt的衣服就是我们最好的选择了
Amazingly, wearing Holt's clothes is our best option.
大家 准备好进入上流社会
Everyone, prepare to enter high society.
大家感觉怎么样
Okay, how's everybody feeling?
有人像我一样非常想对自己说教吗
Anyone else have the weird urge to lecture themselves?
"Peralta 你在做什么"
"Peralta, what are you doing?"
Peralta 你在做什么
Peralta, what are you doing?
我召唤出了Holt
I conjured him.
Holt警监 真是一个美好的惊喜啊
Captain Holt! What a pleasant surprise.
Gina告诉我发生了一些电路故障 你会迟一点来
Gina told me that you were delayed due to a wire situation.
情况是这样的 就算你把所有电线都拔出来
Yes, the situation is, you can rip them all out
车子还是能开
but the car still works.
抱歉啊 兄弟
Sorry, boo.
等等 为什么整个小队都在这里
Wait, why is the whole squad here?
而且每个人都穿着我的衣服
And why is everyone wearing my clothes?
天呐
My God.
你弄丢了Cheddar
You lost Cheddar.
你究竟是怎么猜到的
How did you do that?
长官 我知道你很生气
Sir, I know you're upset,
但是我保证我们会找到Cheddar的
but I promise you we can find Cheddar
你还是可以去巴黎
and you can still go to Paris.
我不去巴黎了
I'm not going to Paris.
现在把我的衣服脱下来
Now, get out of my clothes.
穿上你们自己的衣服
Get into your clothes.
离开我的房子
Get out of my house.
坐进你们自己的车
Get into your cars...
好的 我们懂你的意思
All right, we can take it from there.
非常清楚 再说一次我们真的很抱歉
Loud and clear. Once again, so sorry.
他对我们好失望
Oh, he's so disappointed.
我很抱歉把你们牵扯进来
Look, I'm sorry that I got you involved in this.
我不应该自告奋勇的
I never should have volunteered us.
不 Jake 这不是你的错
No, Jake. It's not your fault.
- 都怪Amy  - 什么
- It's Amy's. - What?
这又不是我的错
Well, it's not my fault.
- 我瞎了  - 额
- Blind. - Ugh.
又不是Jake让Cheddar
And Jake's not the one who let Cheddar
在Kevin的毛衣上尽情撒欢的
go to town on Kevin's sweaters.
拜托 又不是我要喂它Kevin的毛衣
Please, it's not like I fed him Kevin's sweaters.
等一下 大伙 我觉得这是Kevin的错
Wait a minute, guys. I think this is Kevin's fault.
不 Jake 这是Amy的错
No, Jake, it's Amy's.
我知道你想做一个好的男友
I know you're trying to be a cool boyfriend...
这也是另一个原因为什么这事不怪你
yet another reason why it's not your fault...
但是Kevin在巴黎
but Kevin's in Paris.
正是这样我才说这是Kevin的错
Exactly, and that's why I think it's Kevin's fault.
我有一个主意可以找到Cheddar
I have an idea of how to find Cheddar.
Amy 我这么说你一定要矜持住
Amy, don't act weird when I say this,
我们需要用到那个活页夹
but we're gonna need to use the binder.
噢妈呀
Oh, Mama.
Diaz
Diaz!
- 我们能谈一谈吗  - 你想干什么Pimento
- Could we talk? - What do you want, Pimento?
听着 警长给了我一些非常好的建议
Listen, Sarge gave me some really great advice.
所以 Rosa Diaz
So, Rosa Diaz,
你愿意嫁给我吗
will you marry me?
什么
What?
是你叫我这么做的
This is what you told me to do!
我都没说上话
I barely said anything!
你太早打断我了
You cut me off way too early.
警长 别插手
Sarge, stay out of this.
非常乐意
Gladly.
不 我不会嫁给你
No, I will not marry you.
不如我们先去喝一杯怎么样
How about we just get a drink first?
好 好 听起来不错
Yeah. Yeah, that sounds nice.
噢 倒还真不错
Oh, that's actually sweet.
哦不
Nope.
他在这儿呢
Oh, there he is.
Holt警监 他听不见我
Captain Holt! Oh, he can't hear me.
额
Eh...
好了 我大概猜到那些电线是做什么用的了
Okay, well, I guess we know what those wires did.
我没心情听你扯蛋 Peralta.
I'm not in the mood for your antics, Peralta.
长官
Sir, sir!
我觉得我知道Cheddar在哪里
I think we know where Cheddar is.
拜托你上车
Will you please just get in the car?
哦 我来帮你
Oh, let me get that.
现在试试
Try now.
我控制不了这个车锁
Oh, I can't control the locks.
等等 现在试试 一二三
Hang on. Try now. One, two, three.
现在试试 现在试试 我们来救你啦Cheddar
Try now. Try now. Here we come, Cheddar!
现在试试 我们来救你啦Cheddar
Try now. Here we come, Cheddar!
现在 就现在
Try now. Try now.
再试试 我们来救你啦Cheddar
Try now. Here we come, Cheddar!
现在呢
Try now.
Cheddar
Cheddar!
过来吧 宝贝
Come here, baby.
乖 乖
Yeah, yeah.
见到你真高兴
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
你怎么知道它在这
How did you know he was here?
Cheddar只咬Kevin的东西
Well, Cheddar was only chewing up Kevin's stuff.
我想它这样做
I figured maybe he was acting out
是因为他想Kevin了
because he missed Kevin.
但是真正的英雄是那个活页夹
But the real hero here is the binder.
在"Cheddar"分录的子分录"遛狗"下面
Under "Cheddar," Subsection "Walk,"
的子分录"Kevin遛狗"中
subsection "Walks with Kevin,"
我们找到了这个特殊的地方
we found this special spot.
所以你是想Kevin了是吗
So you're missing Kevin, huh?
你不是一个人
You're not the only one.
我取消旅程不是因为我担心
I didn't cancel my trip because I was worried
你会把我的房子给烧了
you would burn my house down.
Kevin和我这段时间关系很僵
Kevin and I are having a hard time right now.
我们一聊天就吵起来
Whenever we talk, we fight.
我只是很担心
And I'm just afraid and just...
担心我去了巴黎我们又会吵起来然后
just afraid that if I go to Paris and we fight, then...
长官 恕我直言 你这个想法很傻
Sir, with all due respect, that's crazy.
你和Kevin是我认识的最棒的伴侣
I mean, you and Kevin are the best couple I know.
而且
And...
我相信不论发生什么你们都会熬过去的
I'm sure whatever this is, you can get through it,
因为你是我认识的最坚强的人
because you are the strongest person I know.
哇这感觉真奇怪 我说了一大堆真心话
Wow, that was weird; I said, like, multiple
而且是连续不停的说
real things consecutively, yeah.
感觉很怪又很棒 你为我感到骄傲吗
Felt weird but good. Are you proud of me?
- 你再说就毁了  - 好
- You're ruining it. - Yup.
我决定闭嘴了
I'm just gonna stop talking now.
看来我不能靠逃避解决任何问题
Well, I suppose I'm not gonna solve anything by running away from it.
也许我应该去巴黎
Perhaps I should go to Paris.
你怎么看 Cheddar
What do you think, Cheddar? Huh?
哦 天啊 你真是一点都藏不住激动之情啊
Oh, my, oh! You really are acting out!
很抱歉让你们看到这一幕
Whew! I'm sorry you had to see that.
噢
Oh.
你们知道吗
You know,
正是这样的时刻
it's moments like these
让我特别感激你们
that I'm grateful for your...
伙计们 简直是奇迹啊
Guys, it's a miracle!
我又可以看见了
I can see!
- 现在不是时候 Charles  - 闭嘴
- Not now, Charles! - Shut up!
哦对 抱歉
Right, sorry!
抱歉
Sorry.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组